Office of Communications and Marketing Records UA252
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Publications, 1998 -- 2007; UA252.004; 4.2 Linear Feet
  - Tufts Medicine Winter 2006, UA252.004.016.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Tufts Medicine Spring 2006, UA252.004.016.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Tufts Medicine Summer 2006, UA252.004.016.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Tufts Medicine Winter 2007, UA252.004.016.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Tufts Nutrition Spring 2001, UA252.004.016.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Tufts Nutrition Fall 2001, UA252.004.016.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Tufts Nutrition Spring 2002, UA252.004.016.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Tufts Nutrition Fall 2002, UA252.004.016.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Tufts Nutrition Spring 2003, UA252.004.016.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Tufts Nutrition Fall 2003, UA252.004.016.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Tufts Nutrition Spring 2004, UA252.004.016.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Tufts Nutrition Fall 2004, UA252.004.016.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Tufts Nutrition Spring 2005, UA252.004.017.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Tufts Nutrition Fall 2005, UA252.004.017.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Tufts Nutrition Spring 2006, UA252.004.017.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Tufts Dental Summer 1999, UA252.004.017.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Tufts Dental Winter 2000, UA252.004.017.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Tufts Dental Summer 2001, UA252.004.017.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Tufts Dental Med. Winter 2001, UA252.004.017.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Tufts Dental Med. Summer 2002, UA252.004.017.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Tufts Dental Med. Winter 2002, UA252.004.017.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Tufts Dental Med. Summer 2003, UA252.004.017.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Dental Corporate Brochure 2002, UA252.004.017.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Tufts Dental Winter 2003, UA252.004.017.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Tufts Dental Summer 2004, UA252.004.017.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Tufts Dental Summer 2005, UA252.004.017.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Tufts Dental Winter 2006, UA252.004.014.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Tufts Dental Summer 2006, UA252.004.014.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Tufts Dental Summer 2007, UA252.004.014.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Tufts Dental Winter 2007, UA252.004.014.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - CDs and DVDs, circa 1998 -- 2007; UA252.004.036; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box Shared 148)
    This file is open for research, but is minimally processed and may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
- Faculty files, 1946 -- 2018; UA252.005; 18 Linear Feet
  This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This series may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
  This series contains files about Tufts faculty compiled by the Office of Communications and Marketing. Files include photographs, newspaper clippings, correspondence, publications, event programs, press releases, personnel records, resumes and other biographical information, course materials and notes, research and project proposals and reports, obituaries, and other materials.
  - Abbott, Daniel, 1971 -- 1983; UA252.005.018.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Abramson, Daniel, 1998 -- 1999; UA252.005.018.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Abu-moustafa, Adel H., 1977 -- 1977; UA252.005.018.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Acheson, David, 1996 -- 1998; UA252.005.018.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Adams, Charles Francis, 1984 -- 1984; UA252.005.018.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Adler, David, 1997 -- 1998; UA252.005.018.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Adomeit, Hannes, 1990 -- 1990; UA252.005.018.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Afrow, Jay, 1990 -- 1990; UA252.005.018.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Afsar, Mohammad Nurul, 1989 -- 1993; UA252.005.018.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Agyeman, Julian, 1993 -- 2003; UA252.005.018.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Ahmed, Igbal, 1990 -- 1990; UA252.005.018.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Akiba, Tadatoshi, 1979 -- 1984; UA252.005.018.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Albertini, David, 1987 -- 1989; UA252.005.018.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Acacia Alcivar-Warren, 1993 -- 2000; UA252.005.018.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Alfaro, Gustavo, 1978 -- 1979; UA252.005.018.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Alexander, David, 1978 -- 1983; UA252.005.018.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Allara, Pamela, 1980 -- 1986; UA252.005.018.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Allen, Bertha, 1981 -- 1981; UA252.005.018.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Allen, Betty, 2000 -- 2000; UA252.005.018.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Astier, Almedom, 2001 -- 2001; UA252.005.018.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Alonzo, Juan Manuel, 1970 -- 2004; UA252.005.018.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Alvarez, Jose, 1994 -- 1994; UA252.005.018.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Alwan, Mohammed, 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.018.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Amir, Amihood, 1984 -- 1984; UA252.005.018.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Ammons, Elizabeth, 1981 -- 1991; UA252.005.018.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Anderson, Mary Ann, 1989 -- 1989; UA252.005.018.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Anderson, Molly, 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.018.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Anderson, Thomas Jefferson, 1973 -- 1985; UA252.005.018.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Androphy, Elliot, 1990 -- 1990; UA252.005.018.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Anwer, Sawkat, 1986 -- 1999; UA252.005.018.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Aprille, June, 1980 -- 2001; UA252.005.018.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Aqua, Ed, 1993 -- 1996; UA252.005.018.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Arana, George W/, 1986 -- 1986; UA252.005.018.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Arbree, Nancy, 1997 -- 1998; UA252.005.018.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Arias, Irwin M., 1985 -- 1998; UA252.005.018.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 35)
    photos/newspaper clippings/letters/event program
  - Arnott, Peter D., 1969 -- 1991; UA252.005.018.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 36)
    photos/newspaper clippings/programs/letters
  - Aronson, Michael, 1997 -- 1998; UA252.005.018.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Asch, Robert, 1965 -- 1965; UA252.005.018.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 38)
    75 years from date of creation.
    photos/newspaper clippings/personnel record
  - Ascher, Gloria J., 1966 -- 1986; UA252.005.018.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 39)
    photos/newspaper clippings/press release/ personnel record
  - Askinas, Walter, 1995 -- 1997; UA252.005.018.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Astill, Kenneth, 1963 -- 1990; UA252.005.018.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 41)
    photos/newspaper clippings/letter
  - Atkins, Floyd, 1993 -- 2000; UA252.005.018.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 42)
    photos/letters/emails
  - Aulenback, Larry, 1993 -- 2000; UA252.005.018.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Ausman, Lynne M., 1984 -- 1995; UA252.005.018.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 44)
    photos/newspaper clippings/bio sheet
  - Aymer, Paula, 1998 -- 1998; UA252.005.018.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Babbit, Eileen, 1997 -- 2016; UA252.005.018.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Bachovchin, William W., 1983 -- 1987; UA252.005.018.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 47)
    newspaper clippings
  - Bacow, Lawerence S., 2001 -- 2004; UA252.005.018.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 48)
    photos/newspaper clippings event programs/emails/bio sheet
  - Baden, Brett, 2005 -- 2005; UA252.005.018.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Baffoni-Licata, Laura, 1998 -- 1999; UA252.005.018.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Bailey, Diana, 1990 -- 1992; UA252.005.018.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Bailey, Stephen, 1985 -- 1996; UA252.005.018.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Balbach, Edith, 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.018.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Ball, Harrison, 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.018.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Balmuth, Miriam, 1964 -- 1991; UA252.005.018.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 55)
    photos/newspaper clippings/letters/notes/event programs/bio sheet
  - Baloueff, Olga, 1987 -- 2001; UA252.005.018.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Bamer, Linda, 1982 -- 1983; UA252.005.018.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Bambrick, Gail, 1990 -- 2016; UA252.005.018.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Barnewolt, Brien, 1998 -- 1998; UA252.005.018.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Barnet, Sylvan, 1962 -- 1985; UA252.005.018.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 60)
    photos/newspaper clippings/personnel record/letters
  - Barnes, William, 1979 -- 1987; UA252.005.018.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Baratz, Robert, 1989 -- 1989; UA252.005.018.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Barach, Howard, 2000 -- 2000; UA252.005.018.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Banks, Peter A., 1987 -- 1992; UA252.005.018.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Banks, Henry H., 1983 -- 1990; UA252.005.018.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Band, Vimla, 1994 -- 1994; UA252.005.018.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Barwell, Nina, 1979 -- 1987; UA252.005.018.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Baskins, Cristelle, 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.018.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Bauer, Janet, 1987 -- 1987; UA252.005.018.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Bauer, Nancy, 1999 -- 2002; UA252.005.018.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 70)
    newspaper clippings/project description
  - Baum, Jules, 1986 -- 1990; UA252.005.018.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Bayne, Sheila, 1993 -- 1993; UA252.005.018.00072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Beardslee, Shiela, 1981 -- 1981; UA252.005.018.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Beardsley, Linda, 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.018.00074; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 74)
    photos, biography
  - Bedau, Hugo Adam, 1966 -- 1997; UA252.005.018.00075; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 75)
    photos/newspaper clippings/letters/research proposals/essays/testimonial records/ bio sheets
  - Bedau, Hugo Adam #2, 1985 -- 1995; UA252.005.019.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Newspaper clippings/photos
  - Beebe, Kathleen, 1981 -- 1984; UA252.005.019.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 2)
    newspaper clippings/photos
  - Beecher, Norman, 1983 -- 1986; UA252.005.019.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Bell, Donald, 1983 -- 1987; UA252.005.019.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 4)
    newspaper clippings/photos/magazine/bio sheet
  - Bell, Susan E., 1980 -- 1981; UA252.005.019.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Newspaper clippings/ curriculum vitae
  - Bellin, Seymour S., 1977 -- 1987; UA252.005.019.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Newspaper clippings/photos/pamphlets/program proposal
  - Benayad-Cherif, F., 1990 -- 1992; UA252.005.019.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Benfari, Robert, 1980 -- 1982; UA252.005.019.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Bennish, Michael, 1998 -- 1999; UA252.005.019.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Photos/article
  - Beson, Dianne, 1990 -- 1991; UA252.005.019.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Berenguer, Angel, 1981 -- 1988; UA252.005.019.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 11)
    Newspaper Clippings/ photos
  - Berg, John, 1987 -- 2000; UA252.005.019.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Berk, Harold, 1986 -- 2001; UA252.005.019.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Berman, Harris, 1987 -- 1987; UA252.005.019.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Bernheim, Harry, 1985 -- 1994; UA252.005.019.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 15)
    Photos, informational letter
  - Bernstein, Jane, 1980 -- 2000; UA252.005.019.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Berry, Dana, 1996 -- 1996; UA252.005.019.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Berry, Jeffery M., 1980 -- 1999; UA252.005.019.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 18)
    newspaper clippings/photos/articles/biosheets
  - Berry, John Curtis, 1987 -- 1987; UA252.005.019.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Bers, Marina, 2001 -- 2001; UA252.005.019.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Bharucha, Jamshed, 2002 -- 2002; UA252.005.019.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 21)
    photos/CD
  - Bianchi, Diana, 1996 -- 2007; UA252.005.019.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Articles/photos
  - Birger, Jordan, 1989 -- 1989; UA252.005.019.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Biswas, Chitra, 1982 -- 1993; UA252.005.019.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Blacher, Richard, 1987 -- 1987; UA252.005.019.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Blagbrough, Richard W., 1980 -- 1993; UA252.005.019.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Block, Steven, 1995 -- 2018; UA252.005.019.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Bloomquist, Eunice, 1984 -- 1984; UA252.005.019.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Blumberg, Jeffery, 1983 -- 1999; UA252.005.019.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 29)
    Newspaper clippings/photos/letter/resume
  - Blumer, Anselm, 1994 -- 2002; UA252.005.019.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Bolden, Jacquelyn, 1996 -- 1996; UA252.005.019.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 31)
    photos/ biography
  - Bono, James, 2003 -- 2003; UA252.005.019.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Borgers, Christoph, 1994 -- 1994; UA252.005.019.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Bose, Sugata, 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.019.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Bosworth, Stephen W., 2000 -- 2001; UA252.005.019.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 35)
    Articles/photos/event program
  - Botsaris, Gregory, 1965 -- 1989; UA252.005.019.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 36)
    photos/newspaper clippings/memo/bio sheet
  - Boudriueu, Randy, 1987 -- 1987; UA252.005.019.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Brantley, Eva, 1981 -- 1985; UA252.005.019.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Bratt, Rachel G., 1981 -- 2000; UA252.005.019.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 39)
    photos/newspaper clippings/curriculum vitae/article
  - Brawer, Barney, 2000 -- 2000; UA252.005.019.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 40)
    newspaper clippings/ photos
  - Brenner, Brian, 2004 -- 2004; UA252.005.019.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Bridges, Robert, 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.019.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Briggs, Cindy, 2000 -- 2000; UA252.005.019.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 43)
    Photos
  - Brinn, Ronald, 1983 -- 1991; UA252.005.019.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 44)
    photos/newspaper clippings/article/project proposal/ biosheet
  - Briss, Barry, 1998 -- 1998; UA252.005.019.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Broadley, Carla, 2005 -- 2005; UA252.005.019.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Broder, Martin, 1992 -- 1992; UA252.005.019.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Broderick, Lillian N., 1982 -- 1993; UA252.005.019.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Brooke, John L., 1980 -- 2000; UA252.005.019.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 49)
    newspaper clippings/ photos/article/bio sheet/seminar plan
  - Brooks, Harvey, 1981 -- 1990; UA252.005.019.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 50)
    newspaper clippings/photos/biography/letter
  - Brooks, Tim, 2000 -- 2016; UA252.005.019.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Brotman, Stuart, 1992 -- 1992; UA252.005.019.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 52)
    newspaper articles/academic papers
  - Brown, Daniel W., 1974 -- 1994; UA252.005.019.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 53)
    newspaper clippings/photos/resume
  - Brown, Drusilla, 1986 -- 1992; UA252.005.019.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 54)
    newspaper clippings/photos/academic paper/bio sheet
  - Brown, Linfield C., 1980 -- 1991; UA252.005.019.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 55)
    newspaper clippings/photos/bio sheet
  - Brown, Phillip (Randy), 1985 -- 1985; UA252.005.019.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 56)
    photo/biography sheet
  - Brown, Richard B., 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.019.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Brugge, Douglas, 1996 -- 2007; UA252.005.019.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 58)
    photos/articles
  - Brush, Ed, 1989 -- 1991; UA252.005.019.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Brustman, Caroline, 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.019.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Bryan, Dale, 1986 -- 2003; UA252.005.019.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Burnim, Kalman A., 1961 -- 1987; UA252.005.019.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 62)
    newspaper clippings/photos/academic paper/notes/letters/student comments/bio sheet/curriculum vitae
  - Busch, Betsy, 1991 -- 1991; UA252.005.019.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Bushnell, Emily W., 1980 -- 1985; UA252.005.019.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 64)
    notes/letters/diagrams/academic papers/articles/curriculum vitae/newspaper clippings/bio sheet
  - Byrne, Joseph J., 1984 -- 1987; UA252.005.019.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 65)
    newspaper clippings/photos/letter/curriculum vitae
  - Callow, Allan D., 1983 -- 1988; UA252.005.019.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 66)
    newspaper clippings/photos/letter/editorial
  - Camara, Kathleen, 1979 -- 1993; UA252.005.019.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 67)
    newspaper clippings/photos/academic papers/research objectives/Journal of Social Issues/curriculum vita
  - Camilli, Andrew, 2002 -- 2002; UA252.005.019.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Cammarata, Paul, 1989 -- 1989; UA252.005.019.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Canny, Elizabeth, 1981 -- 1982; UA252.005.019.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Cantley, Lewis C., 1985 -- 1986; UA252.005.019.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Cantor, Jay, 1977 -- 2003; UA252.005.019.00072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 72)
    newspaper clippings/photos/pamphlet
  - Caplan, Louis, 1987 -- 1996; UA252.005.019.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Carbone, Michele, 1987 -- 1987; UA252.005.019.00074; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 74)
    newspaper clipping
  - Carlisle, Susan, 1985 -- 1986; UA252.005.019.00075; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Carlton, Gregory, 1992 -- 1992; UA252.005.019.00076; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Carr, Daniel, 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.019.00077; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Cartwright, Helen M., 1968 -- 1972; UA252.005.019.00078; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 78)
    photos/personnel records
  - Carzo, Rocco, 1966 -- 2002; UA252.005.019.00079; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 79)
    photos/newspaper clippings/CD/event program/personnel Records/letters/magazines/contact sheets
  - Cataldo, Edmund, 1988 -- 1988; UA252.005.019.00080; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Cavazos, Lauro, 1975 -- 1980; UA252.005.019.00081; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Caviness, Madeline H., 1977 -- 1998; UA252.005.019.00082; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 82)
    photos/newspaper clippings/faculty profile/bio sheet/curriculum vitae/letter/faculty news
  - Cavitch, David, 1972 -- 1986; UA252.005.019.00083; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - Cebe, Peggy, 1998 -- 2004; UA252.005.019.00084; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Chaisson, Eric, 1992 -- 1997; UA252.005.019.00085; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 85)
    photos/newspaper clippings/book jacket/CD
  - Chakravorty, Bonnie, 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.019.00086; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Chang, Chorng Hwa, 1987 -- 2018; UA252.005.019.00087; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 87)
    photo/resume
  - Chang, Te-Wen, 1987 -- 1987; UA252.005.019.00088; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - Chapman, Robert, 1986 -- 2005; UA252.005.019.00089; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 89)
    photos/newspaper clippings/diagrams/article
  - Chapra, Steven, 1999 -- 2000; UA252.005.019.00090; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 90)
    Photos, newspaper clippings, and a certificate.
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Certificate transferred by Tisch Library, January 2022, UA-2023-039.
  - Charm, Stanley, 1980 -- 1982; UA252.005.019.00091; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 91)
  - Charney, Albert, 1987 -- 1987; UA252.005.019.00092; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 92)
    photo/newspaper clippings
  - Chase, Barbara, 1986 -- 1998; UA252.005.019.00093; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 93)
  - Chase, Kerry, 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.019.00094; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 94)
  - Chasin, Werner, 1958 -- 1992; UA252.005.019.00095; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 95)
  - Chatterjee, Sudipto, 2000 -- 2000; UA252.005.019.00096; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 96)
  - Chauncey, Howard, 1989 -- 1989; UA252.005.019.00097; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 97)
  - Chechile, Richard A., 1979 -- 1987; UA252.005.020.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Chen, Li-Li, 1972 -- 1986; UA252.005.020.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 2)
    photos/newspaper clippings/book award news
  - Chen, Nancy, 1993 -- 1993; UA252.005.020.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Chern, Shui-Sheng, 1985 -- 1989; UA252.005.020.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Chikaraishi, Dona, 1987 -- 1987; UA252.005.020.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Cho, Henry H., 1985 -- 1985; UA252.005.020.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Chew, Frances S., 1981 -- 1992; UA252.005.020.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 7)
    photos/newspaper clippings/bio sheet/curriculum vitae
  - Chow, Michael H., 1983 -- 1983; UA252.005.020.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Chudnovsky, Evgenii, 1987 -- 1987; UA252.005.020.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Chudyk, Wayne, 1981 -- 1986; UA252.005.020.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Ciraulo, Domenic, 1986 -- 1987; UA252.005.020.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 11)
    newspaper clippings/news clip data sheet
  - Clark, Eliana DeBernardez, 1998 -- 1998; UA252.005.020.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Clayton, Alan J., 1965 -- 1976; UA252.005.020.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 13)
    newspaper clippings/bio sheet
  - Clemow, Allan H., 1969 -- 1983; UA252.005.020.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 14)
    photos/newspaper clippings/bio sheet/letters/resume
  - Cless, Downing, 1980 -- 1988; UA252.005.020.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 15)
    photos/newspaper clippings/curriculum vitae/bio sheet
  - Cleveland, Richard J., 1980 -- 1987; UA252.005.020.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Cochrane, David E., 1984 -- 1990; UA252.005.020.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Cody, Lisa, 1990 -- 1990; UA252.005.020.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Coffin, John M., 1986 -- 1999; UA252.005.020.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Cohen, Alan, 1993 -- 1993; UA252.005.020.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 20)
    photos/illustration
  - Cohen, Benjamin, 1980 -- 1987; UA252.005.020.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 21)
    photos/newspaper clippings/curriculum vitae/book draft/notes/authors questionnaire
  - Cohn, Ellen S., 1987 -- 1987; UA252.005.020.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Col, Nananda, 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.020.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 23)